What Are You So Afraid Of?
The Hole is a thriller, adventure, fantasy film directed by Joe Dante.
After moving into a new neighbourhood, brothers Dane & Lucas and their
neighbour Julie discover a bottomless hole in the basement of their home.
They find that once the hole is exposed, evil is unleashed.
With strange shadows lurking around every corner and nightmares coming to life, they are forced to
come face to face with their darkest fears to put an end to the mystery of THE HOLE.
Dane Thompson, played by Chris Massoglia.
Lucas Thompson, played by Nathan Gamble.
Julie Campbell, played by Haley Bennett.
Susan Thompson, played by Teri Polo.
Creepy Carl, played by Bruce Dern.
Annie Smith, played by Quinn Lord.
The Hole is a 2009 American 3D dark fantasy horror film directed by Joe Dante and starring
Chris Massoglia, Haley Bennett, Nathan Gamble, Bruce Dern, and Teri Polo.
The film follows two brothers who move into their
new house with their single mother.
The brothers discover a trap door in the basement and accidentally unleash a supernatural
force that manifests itself into any fear of the person who looks into the hole.
Critical reception was largely positive, but the
film was a financial disappointment.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.